Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 4 and District 4 Locals, 1935-1991 UE.4.1.4
ULS Archives & Special Collections
UE National Office Records Relating to District 4 and District 4 Locals
1935-1991
ULS Archives & Special Collections
United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America
UE.4.1.4
14.4 Linear Feet (12 boxes)
This series contains files on United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) District 4 and its locals collected by the UE national office. Included are correspondence, publications, minutes, and news clippings regarding local strikes, events, and organizing efforts.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Previous Citation
UE National Office Records Relating to District 4 and District 4 Locals, 1935-1991, UE.4.1.4, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Scope and Content Notes
District 4 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) consisted of locals throughout the majority of New Jersey and southeastern New York state, including New York City, and are now part of the UE's Eastern Region. This series contains files on UE District 4 and its locals collected by the UE national office. Included are correspondence, publications, minutes, and news clippings regarding local strikes, events, and organizing efforts. Most of the correspondence is between UE national officers and district or local officers.
Arrangement
This series has been arranged into two subseries. The first contains records pertaining to District 4. The other subseries contains records pertaining to specific locals within the district, and are further arranged numerically by local number into sections.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America in 1975, 1986, 1997, and 2001.
Related Material
UE District 4 Records, 1950s, UE.15.4, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
George Kirschner Collection on the American Safety Razor Corporation Strike of 1954, 1952-1972, AIS.1988.16, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- New Jersey -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York -- History; Labor unions -- New Jersey -- History -- 20th century; Labor; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- United States -- History; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- History -- 20th century; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. District 4; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America; Matles, James J.; Emspak, Julius
- District 4, 1.
  - District 4 Constitutions, May-October 1937 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Constituion with May 26, 1937, Max Schroeder Letter to Brothers, May 1937; 1.
    - Constitution, October 30, 1937; 2.
  - District 4 Constitutions, May 1944-October 1946 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Constitution, May 25, 1944; 1.
    - Constitution with October 21, 1946, Walter Barry Letter to James Matles, October 1946; 2.
    - Constitution, 3.
  - District 4 Constitutions, October 26, 1942-January 26, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - District 4 Constitutions, July 24, 1945-October 5, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - District 4 Constitutions, May 11, 1944-February 14, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - District 4 Officers Lists, April 4, 1949-November 7, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - District 4 Executive Board Minutes, July 29, 1940-September 18, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - District 4 Executive Board Minutes, November 27, 1944-September 23, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Executive Board Minutes, November 27, 1944-March 25, 1946; 1-6.
    - Executive Board Minutes with April 5-7, 1946, Declaration and Win the Peace Conference, April 22, 1946; 7.
    - Executive Board Minutes, July 22-September 23, 1946; 8-9.
  - District 4 Executive Board Minutes, October 21, 1946-May 17, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Executive Board Minutes, October 21, 1946; 1.
    - Executive Board Minutes with Statement and Suggested Resolution, December 30, 1946; 2.
    - Executive Board Minutes, February 14-April 14, 1947; 3-5.
    - Executive Board Minutes with Financial Report, May 17, 1947; 6.
  - District 4 Executive Board Minutes, June 4, 1947-May 10, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Executive Board Minutes, June 4-December 8, 1947; 1-6.
    - Executive Board Minutes with Statatement on Automomy of Congress of Industrial Organizations International Unions, February 1, 1948; 7.
    - Executive Board Minutes, March 8-May 10, 1948; 8-10.
  - District 4 Executive Board Minutes, June 14, 1948-May 9, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - District 4 Executive Board Minutes, June 13-October 10, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Executive Board Minutes with Statement on Civil Liberties, June 13, 1949; 1.
    - Executive Board Minutes, July 11-August 8, 1949; 2-3.
    - Executive Board Minutes with Statement of District 4 Executive Board Regarding Peeks Kill Not, September 21, 1949; 4.
    - Executive Board Minutes with September 28, 1949, Frank Motter Letter to James Matles; October 7, 1949, William Senter Statement; October 11, 1949, James McLeish Telegram to McGratz; Leaflet; Statement of Support for Striking Steel and Mine Workers; and October 24, 1949, McLeish Letter to Harry Truman, October 10, 1949; 5.
  - District 4 Executive Board Minutes, November 14, 1949-July 10, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - District 4 Executive Board Minutes, August 14, 1950-March 27, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Executive Board Minutes with Cost of Living Petition and Leaflet, August 14, 1950; 1.
    - Executive Board Minutes, November 13, 1950-July 26, 1951; 2-5.
    - Executive Board Minutes with October 26, 1951, James McLeish Letter to Local Presidents, October 25, 1951; 6.
    - Executive Board Minutes, February 28-March 27, 1952; 7-8.
  - District 4 Executive Board Minutes, March 26, 1953-July 28, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Executive Board Minutes, March 26-28, 1953; 1-2.
    - Executive Board Minutes with District 4 Wage Settlements, June 25, 1953; 3.
    - Executive Board Minutes with Action Taken on Draft Resolutions, July 23, 1953; 4.
    - Executive Board Minutes, January 15, 1954-July 28, 1955; 5-8.
  - District 4 Resolutions, October 21, 1946-July 3, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Infantile Paralysis, October 21, 1946; 1.
    - James Lustig Trial, June 12, 1950; 2.
    - Wages, July 3, 1953; 3.
    - Peace and Jobs, July 3, 1953; 4.
    - UE Policy, July 3, 1953; 5.
    - McCarthyism, July 3, 1953; 6.
    - Organization, July 3, 1953; 7.
    - McCarran Walter Act, July 3, 1953; 8.
  - District 4 Council Minutes, July 10, 1937-June 28, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Council Minutes, July 10, 1937-November 28, 1944; 1-4.
    - Council Minutes with Scott Fletcher Speech, April 26, 1945; 5.
    - Council Minutes, May 24-June 28, 1945; 6-7.
  - District 4 Council Minutes, May 23, 1946-February 27, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Council Minutes, May 23-July 25, 1946; 1-2.
    - Council Minutes with Recommendations for Constitutional Changes, September 26, 1946; 3.
    - Council Minutes, October 27, 1946-February 27, 1947; 4-8.
  - District 4 Council Minutes, March 27-May 22, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Council Minutes with Health and Recreation Fund and Anti-Communism Statement, March 27, 1947; 1.
    - Council Minutes with Analysis of Taft Hartly Bill, April 24, 1947; 2.
    - Council Minutes, May 22, 1947; 3.
  - District 4 Council Minutes, July 24, 1947-July 22, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Council Minutes, July 24, 1947-February 6, 1948; 1-5.
    - Council Minutes with Statement of Deportations, March 28, 1948; 6.
    - Council Minutes, April 22-July 22, 1948; 7-10.
  - District 4 Council Minutes, August 26, 1948-November 9, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Council Minutes, August 26, 1948-September 29, 1949; 1-8.
    - Council Minutes with Statement of District Executive Board, October 15, 1949; 9.
    - Council Minutes with District Council Statement, November 9, 1949; 10.
  - District 4 Council Minutes, January 26-October 26, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Council Minutes with UE Support to the United Mine Workers of America, January 26, 1950; 1.
    - Council Minutes, March 23-July 27, 1950; 2-4.
    - Council Minutes with Sample Post Card, Program of Action and Sample Resolution, August 24, 1950; 5.
    - Council Minutes, September 28-October 26, 1950; 6-7.
  - District 4 Council Minutes, January 25, 1951-December 6, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Council Minutes with Plan of Action for Tax Campaign, January 25, 1951; 1.
    - Council Minutes, February 15, 1951; 2.
    - Council Minutes with Fair Practices Committee Letter to District Council, July 12, 1951; 3.
    - Council Minutes with James McLeish Letter to H.J. McGrath, February 14, 1952; 4.
    - Council Minutes, March 13-December 6, 1952; 5-8.
  - District 4 Council Minutes, April 18, 1953-August 4, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - District 4 Council Resolutions, March 15, 1941-July 25, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Strikes, March 15, 1941; 1.
    - National Labor Relations Board, July 25, 1946; 2.
    - Political Action, July 25, 1946; 3.
    - UE Officers and Factionalism, July 25, 1946; 4.
    - Dues, July 25, 1946; 5.
    - Westinghouse Political Action and Strikes, July 25, 1946; 6.
    - Westinghouse, General Motors and General Electric Strikes, July 25, 1946; 7.
    - Foreign Policy, July 25, 1946; 8.
    - Health, July 25, 1946; 9.
    - Political Action Committee, July 25, 1946; 10.
    - Incentive Pay, July 25, 1946; 11.
    - Contracts, July 25, 1946; 12.
    - Taxation, July 25, 1946; 13.
    - Racism, July 25, 1946; 14.
    - World Federation of Trade Unions, July 25, 1946; 15.
    - Atomic Energy, July 25, 1946; 16.
  - District 4 Council Resolutions, July 24, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Contracts, July 24, 1947; 1.
    - Fair Employment Practices Commission, July 24, 1947; 2.
    - Unemployment, July 24, 1947; 3.
    - Joint Anti-Fascist Refugee Committee, July 24, 1947; 4.
    - Taft-Hartly, July 24, 1947; 5.
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations and Western Electric, July 24, 1947; 6.
    - UE Officers, July 24, 1947; 7.
    - Factionalism, July 24, 1947; 8.
  - District 4 Council Resolutions, July 24, 1947-December 6, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Political Action Committee, July 24, 1947; 1.
    - Foreign Policy, July 24, 1947; 2.
    - Anti-Communism, July 24, 1947; 3.
    - House Un-American Activities Committee, April 22, 1948; 4.
    - UE Program with October 18, 1949, Ruth Young Letter to Albert Fitzgerald, October 15, 1949; 5.
    - Phelps Dodge-Local 441 Trials and Strikes, January 15, 1951; 6.
    - Grand Jury and Anti-Communism, December 6, 1952; 7.
  - District 4 Staff Meeting Minutes, September 7, 1943-February 15, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Staff Meeting Minutes, September 7-November 16, 1943; 1-4.
    - Staff Meeting Minutes with July 12, 1944, Ruth Young Letter to Julius Emspak, July 10, 1944; 5.
    - Staff Meeting Minutes, October 25, 1944-February 15, 1947; 6-10.
  - District 4 Organizers Meeting Minutes, February 28, 1939-July 22, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - District 4 Organizers Meeting Minutes, July 23-October 14, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - District 4 Organizers Meeting Minutes, October 28-December 23, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - District 4 Organizers Meeting Minutes, March 10, 1942-July 11, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Meeting Minutes, March 10-May 26, 1942; 1-3.
    - Meeting Minutes with July 26, 1946, Walter Barry Letter to James Matles, July 11, 1946; 4.
  - District 4 Organizers Meeting Minutes, August 15, 1946-April 26, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - District 4 Lamp and Tube Council, June 6-29, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Minutes, June 6-21, 1949; 1-2.
    - Pauline Royre to James Matles, June 29, 1949; 3.
  - District 4 Westinghouse and General Electric Local Presidents, Minutes, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - District 4 New York Conference Board Minutes, May 1-July 10, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - District 4 Mercer County Conference Board Minutes, January 17-April 25, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - District 4 Legislative Committee, May 21, 1938-January 21, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Legislative Bulletin, May 21, 1938; 1.
    - Political Action Committee Minutes, March 11, 1947; 2.
    - Union County Minutes, December 22, 1948; 3.
    - Committee Minutes, December 28, 1948; 4.
    - New York Committee Minutes with Report of Washington Delegation and New York Representatives in Office, January 19, 1949; 5.
    - New Jersey Committee Chairmen Minutes with Report of Washington Delegation, January 21, 1949; 6.
  - District 4 Fair Practices Committee, "A Challenge to Union Members", March 23, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - District 4 Fair Practices Committee, April 1950-September 24, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - General Electric Foul Practices with April 3, 1950, Ernest Thompson Letter to Local Presidents, April 1950; 1.
    - Committee Minutes, December 6, 1950; 2.
    - Walter Speicher to William Wallace, July 25, 1951; 3.
    - Ben Tiedeman to James McLeish, July 26, 1951; 4.
    - Minutes, August 1, 1951; 5.
    - Joseph Squires to All Fair Employment Practices Commission Members, September 4, 1951; 6.
  - District 4 Unemployment Committee, February-December 1938 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Report with June 27, 1938, William Newman Letter to Julius Emspak, February -June 1938; 1.
    - Report, December 1937-December 1938; 2.
  - District 4 Membership Activities Department, April, 1940-March 31, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Report, April-May, 1940; 1.
    - Report on Hospitalization Plans, June 1940; 2.
    - Ruth Young to New York Local Secretaries, July 8, 1940; 3.
    - Report, March 3, 1942; 4.
    - Report, 5.
  - District 4 Education Committee Curriculum with Ruth Young Letter, March 8, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - District 4 Westchester President and District 3 and 4 Committee Minutes, November 4, 1948-May 15, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Westchester President Minutes, November 4, 1948; 1.
    - District 3 and 4 Womens Committee Minutes, May 15, 1953; 2.
  - District 4 Joseph Dermody Incoming Correspondence, November 1, 1938-August 27, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - James Carey Regarding District Council Meetings, November 28, 1948, December 12, 1949; 1-2.
    - Carey Regarding Liviton Manufacturing Organization, August 5, 1940; 3.
    - Julius Emspak Letter, March 22, 1939; 4.
    - Emspak Regarding Locals 1206 and 1216 and Finances, March 27, 1939; 5.
    - Emspak Regarding Political Action, October 28, 1939; 6.
    - Emspak Regarding District Council Meeting, November 17, 1939; 7.
    - Emspak Regarding Locals 425 and 475, January 13, 1940; 8.
    - Emspak Regarding Sperry Organization, February 29, 1940; 9.
    - Emspak Regarding Amalgamation of Locals 1218 and 1225 with April 5, 1940, Bert Brines Letter to General Executive Board, April 24, 1940; 10.
    - Emspak Regarding Air King, June 19, 1940; 11.
    - Emspak Regarding Passaic, August 27, 1940; 12.
    - James Matles Regarding District Boundaries, November 1, 1938; 13.
    - Matles Letter, November 28, 1938; 14.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, January 3, 1939; 15.
    - Matles Regarding Workmen's Compensation, February 10, 1939; 16.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, March 30, 1939; 17.
    - Matles Regarding Lambert Meter and Runaway Shops, April 27, 1939; 18.
    - Matles Regarding Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians, August 28, 1939; 19.
    - Matles Regarding Supplies, August 16, 1939; 20.
  - District 4 Joseph Dermody Incoming Correspondence, September 25, 1939-November 15, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - James Matles Regarding New York Congress of Industrial Organizations, September 25, 1939; 1.
    - Matles Regarding Political Action with September 26, 1939, Michael Quill Letter to Matles and September 27, 1939, Matles Letter to Quill, September 28, 1939; 2.
    - Matles Letter, November 1, 1939; 3.
    - Matles Regarding EA Laboratories, November 15, 1940; 4.
  - District 4 Joseph Dermody Outgoing Correspondence, March 1938-February 1942 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Dermody to Sisters and Brothers Regarding Rivers Testimonial with Reservation Form, March 17, 1938; 1.
    - Dermody to Sisters and Brothers Regarding Pestolock Runaway Shops and Strikes, March 17, 1938; 2.
    - Dermody to Julius Emspak Regarding Officers Meeting, May 12, 1938; 3.
    - Dermody to James Matles Regarding Jurisdicton Boundaries, October 31, 1938; 4.
    - Dermody to Harry Block Regarding General Motors Jurisdiction, November 15, 1938; 5.
    - Dermody to Matles Regarding GM Jurisdiction, November 15, 1938; 6.
    - Dermody to James Carey Regarding District Council Meeting, November 23, 1938; 7.
    - Dermody to Emspak Regarding District Council Meeting, November 23, 1938; 8.
    - Dermody to Matles Regarding District Council Meeting, November 23, 1938; 9.
    - Dermody to Emspak Regarding Merger of Locals 1206 and 1216, March 22, 1939; 10.
    - Dermody Telegram to Carey Regarding New Jersey Congress of Industrial Organizations, April 25, 1939; 11.
    - Dermody to Matles Regarding Western Electric, August 19, 1939; 12.
    - Dermody to Matles Regarding District Council Meeting, October 31, 1939; 13.
    - Dermody to Emspak Regarding District Council Meeting, October 31, 1939; 14.
    - Dermody to Carey Regarding District Council Meeting, October 31-December 6, 1939; 15-16.
    - Dermody to Al Stearn Regarding Local 1206, February 20, 1940; 17.
    - Dermody to Local 1206 Executive Board Regarding Local 1206 Strikes with Abbey Photos, United Transformer and Sky Chief, April 17, 1940; 18.
    - Dermody to Carey Regarding New York CIO, April 26, 1940; 19.
    - Dermody to Emspak Regarding UE Convention and District 4 Membership Activities, July 12, 1940; 20.
    - Dermody to Carey Regarding Leviton Organization, August 1, 1940; 21.
    - Dermody to Matles Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Anaconda Organization with January 31, 1942, George Myer Letter to Dermody, February 1942; 22.
  - District 4 Kate Heck Incoming Correspondence, July 2, 1943-July 6, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Janet Barish Regarding Finances, July 2, 1943-November 16, 1948; 1-14.
    - Barish Regarding UE News, July 6, 1949; 15.
    - William Cahn Regarding Strikes and African Americans, January 25, 1946; 16.
    - Cahn Regarding Films, December 22, 1948; 17.
    - Cahn Regarding Education with Fannie Cohn Letter to Bernice Rosen, May 18, 1948; 18.
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Local 108 Per Capita, April 17, 1945; 19.
    - Emspak Regarding Stewards, February 6, 1948; 20.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, March 11, 1949; 21.
    - Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Local 1217 Constitution, May 14, 1945; 22.
    - Fitzgerald Regarding Local 410 Constitution, March 21, 1944; 23.
    - Fitzgerald Regarding Resolutions, November 12, 1944; 24.
  - District 4 Kate Heck Incoming Correspondence, August 11, 1943-June 24, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Helen Lief Regarding Strikes with List of Strikes Since V-J Day, May 23, 1946; 1.
    - Fredrick Livingston Regarding Conscription, May 11, 1945; 2.
    - Ed Matthews Regarding Local 408 Incentive, August 11, 1943; 3.
    - Don Pinkston Regarding Supplies, April 28, 1947; 4.
    - Pinkston Regarding Literature with Sales of "We Took Our Fight to the People", June 24, 1947; 5.
    - David Ratner Regarding Supplies, November 16, 1944; 6.
    - Ratner Regarding Finances, January 16, 1947; 7.
    - Ratner Regarding Organization Finances with District 4 Colonizers, January 19, 1947; 8.
    - Ratner Regarding Finances, March 3-May 28, 1947; 9-10.
    - Letter with May 29, 1946, Julius Emspak Letter to Thomas Nivens and May 16, May 28 and June 6, 1946, Nivens Letters to Emspak, 11.
    - Letter Regarding Local 408 Amalgamation, November 14, 1946; 12.
  - District 4 Kate Heck Outgoing Correspondence, February 9, 1943-April 17, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Heck to Nate Geller Regarding Finances, February 9, 1943; 1.
    - Heck to Norma Gould Regarding Women's Literature, March 9, 1943; 2.
    - Heck to Janet Barish Regarding Finances, May 11, 1943; 3.
    - Heck to Edward Matthews Regarding Local 408 Incentive, August 4, 1943; 4.
    - Heck to Geller Regarding Education, January 3, 1944; 5.
    - Heck to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, January 16-April 2, 1945; 6-10.
    - Heck to Clara Hall Regarding Mailing List, April 20, 1945; 11.
    - Heck to Barish Regarding Senate Education and Labor Committee Finances, October 10, 1945; 12.
    - Heck to Don Pinkston Regarding Publicity Finances, January 15, 1946; 13.
    - Heck to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, April 4-October 2, 1946; 14-15.
    - Heck to David Ratner Regarding Finances, October 2, 1946; 16.
    - Heck to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, October 11, 1946; 17.
    - Heck to UE Regarding Staff Members, November 27, 1946; 18.
    - Heck to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, February 8, 1947; 19.
    - Heck to Ratner Regarding Organization Finances, March 4, 1947; 20.
    - Heck to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, March 7, 1947; 21.
    - Heck to Ratner Regarding Organization Finances, March 7, 1947; 22.
    - Heck to Ray Klausner Regarding Mailing List, April 7, 1947; 23.
    - Heck to Ratner Regarding Political Action Committee, April 11, 1947; 24.
    - Heck to Ratner Regarding Finances, April 17, 1947; 25.
  - District 4 Kate Heck Outgoing Correspondence, April 21, 1947-August 10, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Heck to David Ratner Regarding Finances, April 21, 1947; 1.
    - Heck to Ratner Regarding Western Electric Organization, May 9, 1947; 2.
    - Heck to Ratner Regarding Organization Publicity with Leaflet Lists, May 22, 1947; 3.
    - Heck to Ratner Regarding National Pneumatic Finances, May 28, 1947; 4.
    - Heck to Joseph Platsky Regarding Staff Members, August 20, 1947; 5.
    - Heck to Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, October 27, 1947; 6.
    - Heck to Fanny Cohen Regarding Supplies, November 5, 1947; 7.
    - Heck to Tom Wright Regarding Mailing List, February 10, 1948; 8.
    - Heck to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, August 13, 1948; 9.
    - Heck to Ratner Regarding Local 427 Finances, November 23, 1948; 10.
    - Heck to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, November 24, 1948-January 2, 1949; 11-12.
    - Heck to Ratner Regarding Anaconda Finances, May 18, 1949; 13.
    - Heck to Barish Regarding Staff Finances, June 17, 1949; 14.
    - Heck to Barish Regarding Local 401 Singer Strike, August 10, 1949; 15.
  - District 4 James Lustig Incoming Correspondence, February 21, 1938-January 2, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Janet Barish Regarding Otis Elevator Finances, January 2, 1952; 1.
    - Willard Bliss Regarding Clemson Brothers Strike, May 12, 1942; 2.
    - Harry Block Regarding District 4 Radio Council Organization, February 21, 1938; 3.
    - Neil Brant Regarding War Labor Board, May 22, 1943; 4.
    - H.N. Broxon Regarding Phelps Dodge Strike, January 4, 1946; 5.
    - James Carey Regarding Local 1227 Factionalism, January 24, 1939; 6.
    - Carey Regardng Local 1214 Lambert Meter Strike, February 25, 1939; 7.
    - Carey Regarding Phelps Dodge, August 23, 1939; 8.
    - Lyle Dowling Regarding New York City Congress of Industrial Organizations, January 16, 1942; 9.
    - Dowling Regarding "Win the War" Conference and Political Action, June 24, 1942; 10.
    - Dowling Regarding UE News and Literature, June 30, 1942; 11.
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Defunct Locals, April 26, 1938; 12.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 1233, May 9, 1938; 13.
    - Emspak with Emspak Letter to D.F. Stanley, May 23, 1938; 14.
    - Emspak Regarding Camera Industry and Bell and Howell Organization, June 22, 1938; 15.
    - Emspak Regarding Boycotts, July 30, 1938; 16.
    - Emspak Regarding District 4 Annual Dance, September 23, 1938; 17.